[
  {
    "name": "Allena",
    "precedingDialogue": [
      "Many world leaders are demanding more radical climate change initiatives",
      "In response, the council wants to ban all vehicles for 1 week."
    ],
    "question": "Do you allow this to happen?",
    "options": [
      {
        "label": "Yes, I think we should the world a message",
        "happiness": -15,
        "environment": 10,
        "npcName": "Allena",
        "feedback": "The town is not happy. On the flip side, the air has become cleaner."
      },
      {
        "label": "No this is a drastic, lets just do one day",
        "happiness": -5,
        "environment": 3,
        "npcName": "Allena",
        "feedback": "The town is not happy. On the flip side, the air has become cleaner."
      },
      {
        "label": "Not at all, this would be terrible for the economy",
        "money": 3,
        "happiness": 4,
        "environment": -5,
        "npcName": "Allena",
        "feedback": "The townspeople's daily routines were not disrupted, but emissions kept going up. "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Allena",
    "sliderType": true,
    "precedingDialogue": [
      "The increasing population of our town has increased our CO2 emission levels",
      "The local environmentalists wishes for funding to plant trees to counteract the effects."
    ],
    "question": "How much money do you provide to the tree planting initiative?",
    "maxValue": 100,
    "minValue": 0,
    "options": [
      {
        "threshold": 50,
        "money": -20,
        "environment": 25,
        "hasAnimation": true,
        "buildingName": "Trees",
        "feedback": "The environmentalists are very grateful for your support, it's made a marked improvement on the environment",
        "npcName": "Allena"
      },
      {
        "threshold": 25,
        "money": -10,
        "happiness": 5,
        "environment": 5,
        "hasAnimation": true,
        "buildingName": "Trees",
        "feedback": "The environmentalists are thankful for your funding, but more funding could've made more of a difference",
        "npcName": "Allena"
      },
      {
        "threshold": 0,
        "label": "No",
        "environment": -25,
        "happiness": -10,
        "feedback": "The environmentalists are very upset, as the pollutions were not helped",
        "npcName": "Allena"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Jimmy Cash",
    "question": "We are spending more fossil fuels than we import. Do we restrict the number of cars on the road?",
    "options": [
      {
        "label": "Yes",
        "happiness": -10
      },
      {
        "label": "No",
        "money": -15
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "James the Dog",
    "question": "People want public transport to be free for the upcoming holiday. Do you allow this to happen?",
    "options": [
      {
        "label": "Yes",
        "money": -15,
        "happiness": 10,
        "environment": 5,
        "npcName": "James the Dog",
        "feedback": "The people are happy and there were less cars on the road too."
      },
      {
        "label": "No",
        "happiness": -5,
        "environment": -5,
        "npcName": "James the Dog",
        "feedback": "The people are not too happy with you for not supporting their holidays. "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Advisory Board",
    "question": "The council wants to train teachers to educate children about climate change. Do you allow this to happen?",
    "options": [
      {
        "label": "Yes",
        "money": -10,
        "environment": 5,
        "npcName": "Advisory Board",
        "feedback": "The children are more aware of climate change now, they've made an effort to protect the environment. "
      },
      {
        "label": "No",
        "npcName": "Advisory Board",
        "feedback": "Even though educating children can be expensive, it's definitely a worthy investment. "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Allena",
    "question": "A local merchant Bob K. has spread rumour around the town that climate change is fake. What do you do?",
    "options": [
      {
        "label": "Ignore",
        "happiness": -10,
        "environment": -15,
        "npcName": "Allena",
        "feedback": "The rumour spread wide and loud, townspeople began not treating climate change seriously. It took a while before they found out it was not true. "
      },
      {
        "label": "Educate the townspeople",
        "money": -15,
        "happiness": 5,
        "environment": 10,
        "npcName": "Allena",
        "feedback": "It took a small educational campaign, but the townspeople are thankful for the clarification. "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Advisory Board",
    "question": "The neighbouring town has a shortage of timber. Do you want to sell your trees to them?",
    "options": [
      {
        "label": "Yes",
        "happiness": -5,
        "environment": -10,
        "money": 10,
        "npcName": "Advisory Board",
        "feedback": "Selling timber is a good short term financial decision, but cutting down trees harms the environment. "
      },
      {
        "label": "No",
        "npcName": "Advisory Board",
        "feedback": "That was a very neutral decision. "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "James the Dog",
    "question": "The townspeople want to have a bonfire for an all night out doors music festive. Do you allow this?",
    "options": [
      {
        "label": "Yes",
        "happiness": 10,
        "environment": -10,
        "npcName": "James the Dog",
        "feedback": "It's sometimes hard to balance what to do isn't it"
      },
      {
        "label": "No",
        "happiness": -10,
        "npcName": "James the Dog",
        "feedback": "It's sometimes hard to balance what to do isn't it"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Jimmy Cash",
    "question": "There are still too many cars on the road. Do you want to increase the petrol tax?",
    "options": [
      {
        "label": "Yes",
        "happiness": -10,
        "environment": 5,
        "money": 10,
        "npcName": "Jimmy Cash",
        "feedback": "People aren't very happy with the new rule, but it has helped reduce emissions"
      },
      {
        "label": "No",
        "environment": -10,
        "npcName": "Jimmy Cash",
        "feedback": "Emissions kept going up, polluting the city air"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Allena",
    "question": "The city is generating a lot of rubbish, how should we treat them?",
    "options": [
      {
        "label": "Build another landfill",
        "happiness": -10,
        "environment": -15,
        "npcName": "Allena",
        "hasAnimation": true,
        "buildingName": "LandFill",
        "feedback": "Landfills release a lot of bad gas into the environment, and it's making the local people unhappy. "
      },
      {
        "label": "Recycle the rubbish",
        "environment": 15,
        "money": "-10",
        "happiness": "10",
        "npcName": "Allena",
        "feedback": "Even though recycling rubbish is expensive, it is very good for the environment. "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Jimmy Cash",
    "question": "An international corporation is wanting to setup a chemical factory in the city, should we let them??",
    "options": [
      {
        "label": "Yes",
        "environment": -10,
        "money": 25,
        "npcName": "Jimmy Cash",
        "hasAnimation": true,
        "buildingName": "ChemicalFactory",
        "feedback": "The city gets a lot more tax from the factory, but also taking a lot of pollution from them. "
      },
      {
        "label": "No",
        "npcName": "Jimmy Cash",
        "feedback": "The company leaves you alone. "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "First Plebeian",
    "question": "Help! Our house got burnt down in a fire, we have nowhere to live now. ",
    "options": [
      {
        "label": "Lend them a hand. ",
        "money": -5,
        "happiness": 5,
        "npcName": "First Plebeian",
        "feedback": "The plebeian thanks you! "
      },
      {
        "label": "That's the insurance company's job. ",
        "happiness": -5,
        "npcName": "First Plebeian",
        "feedback": "The plebeian resents you "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Second Plebeian",
    "question": "Mayor, can you come give a speech at my daughter's high school's graduation? ",
    "options": [
      {
        "label": "It would be my pleasure",
        "happiness": 5,
        "npcName": "Second Plebeian",
        "feedback": "The plebeian and his daughter thanks you! "
      },
      {
        "label": "Sorry I'm too busy.  ",
        "happiness": -5,
        "npcName": "Second Plebeian",
        "feedback": "The plebeian understands.  "
      }
    ]
  }
]
